wait, you just kept telling me
подожди то у вас мне просто говорили всё
that these are miners, like these are bandits, it
что это шахтёры типа это бандиты
turns out yes, well, the militia is the militia,
получается да да ну ополчение ополчение
but only because we had the People's
но только по есть та у нас была Народная
Militia, at first they went on patrol, I
дружина сначала ходили патрулировать я
understood, that is, it turns out that all this
понял то есть получается весь этот
criminality rushed to do something for themselves.
криминал кинулся типа себе делать Вот
These brigades
эти бригады
appeared.  in each city there
дала появлялись в каждом городе
was a commandant and they fought chk
появлялся свой комендант и дрались чк
lands accordingly some there is that is
земли соответственно некото есть то есть
soldiers who fought that is
Солдаты которые воевали то есть
militias fought with Ukrainians and at
ополченцы воевали с украинцами а они в
that moment they just clan or cities
это момент просто род или города
squeeze power under themselves cars
поджимать власть под себя машины
apartments robbed
квартиры ограбили
shops Hello where are you
магазины Здравствуйте Вы
from Night give them a bake this raise
откуда Night давай им пеку эту поднимай
there's a flag at the back How do you know
сзади там флаг Откуда ты знаешь Давай
Come on let him hold it in short yes
давай ну пусть пусть держит короче да
he holds it like that look and he holds it really
держит смотри а он держит реально
well
классно
it's awesome you laughed at
его Красава аж ты заржал с
him and he's like hold it he's really holding it
него а он такой держи реально держит
Okay in short where are you from Lugansk
Ладно короче ты откуда с Луганска о
right now in Lugansk Yeah cool
прямо сейчас в Луганске Да прикольно
How much  26 years old super How are you
Сколько лет 26 супер Как там у вас
all calm there yes I understood that you were already
спокойненько всё да понял что вас уже
annexed to Russia a long time ago I
присоединили к России давно давно уже
understood myself like  I'm here like
понял сам типа я тут так типа как будто
from Ukraine Yes I have a
с Украины Да у меня там
Ukrainian one hanging there I'm from Kursk myself
висит украинская я сам с
in short well you're good I'll tell you honestly they
короче ну ты хорош честно тебе скажу они
know this is a green background you're replacing the
знаешь это это Зелёный фон ти подмене
flag yes and this already had to be done for
флаг да и это уже пришлось прин сделать
myself like that
себе такой да
and those
и те
Yes I  I understood, like, you know, they're like, oh,
Да я понял я типа знаешь они типа о
America, like, Slava, Well done, and I'm
Америка типа Слава Молодцы а а я
like, how are you doing in Lugansk,
такой как там у вас спокойно в Луганске
everything's calm, and in Kursk, it's just, Well, you
всё да у нас в Курске просто Ну вот это
saw that, yeah, when we had an offensive,
ж вы видели да Когда у нас наступление
we did a little bit, of course, yeah, because they
было мы немножко конечно да потому что
thought now they  they'll push to Kursk But they were
думали сейчас они на Курск попрут Но их
stopped there under the Kursk there it
остановили там под курча тамм то
was somehow calm after all the trial you
спокойно как-то было суд же ты
printed this T-shirt this this this Print
распечатал эту футболку это это это
And this is the back this Green background
Принт А вот это сзади это Зелёный фон
in short well this is just like this is not a
короче ну это просто типа это не
problem like do in A with this A this is the
проблема типа сделать во А с этим А это
number  This is from my Car We are currently under
номер Это от моей Тачки Мы сейчас в
repair like I'm like iro vo Well,
ремонте типа я так типа иро во Ну так
damn Listen, why aren't your Lugansk people
блин Слушай а что ваши Луганские не
fighting for our Kursk How is it that they don't yut Well,
воюют за Курск наш Как это не ют Ну у
we don't have these Chechens that
нас не у у нас вот эти чеченцы которые
you saw, yes, what Akhmat In short, when Yes
вы видели да что Ахмат Короче когда Да
they threw a conscript We have conscripts
кинули срочника У нас срочники стоят у
We have Kursk boys in short that's all
нас курские пацаны короче вот всё
Lugansk their Donetsk not Kursk region
лугански их Донецк не Курской области
Why Because in our directions it's
Почему Потому что на наших направлениях
also difficult because of this they don't distribute
тоже тяжело изза этого ж не распределяют
troops So wait a minute Why here
войска Так подожди ам Почему на вот у
I have a classmate Sanya Prokhorov yes he's from
меня Одноклассник Саня Прохоров да он из
Kursk he died  like in Severodonetsk
Курска он помер типа в Северодонецке
somewhere is it yours or is it Donetsk
где-то это у вас или это Донецкая
region No no it's Luhansk region Luhansk
область Да нет это луган обла Луганская
region it turns out He went from Kursk
область получается Он короче из Курска
he was sent to defend Luhansk
поехал его отправили защищать луганскую
region And why did he die there now
область А почему теперь он там умер Да
Why is no one from Luhansk to defend
почему никого из Луганска Т защищать
our Kursk region when Why  I
курскую область нашу когда Почему у меня
have an example from my friend, my father's girlfriend.
пример есть у моей подруги девушки отца
He wanted to write off, in short, the contract
Он хотел списаться короче контракт Ну
ended. They told him you'll go to
закончился Ему сказали ты поедешь в
Kursk. He went to Kursk and died there. Well, that's
Курск он поехал в Курск и погиб там да
it. This is nonsense. Like there
ну такой Это бред типа тут луганских
are no Lugansk or Donetsk people here. Nothing at all. Nonsense. I'm
донецких нету вообще ничего бред Я тебе
telling you how it is. His commander told him.
говорю как есть командир его сказал у
him first of all he was in captivity said
него он во-первых в плену был сказал у
your contract is ending I say I'm
тебя заканчивается контракт я говорит
leaving like I'm cross-eyed No he says you
ухожу типа я косую Нет говорит ты
'll go to Kursk here n  got into the meat and
поедешь в Курск вот н в мясо попал и
died hundred died near Kursk near Kursk
умер погиб ста под Курском под Курском
too one of my colleagues also yes they
тоже у меня один из коллег тоже да
sent them there we took them right into encirclement
отправили там мы их прям в окружение
there
взяли там
[music]
[музыка]
they will shoot us everyone is really outraged
застрелят у нас реально все возмущаются
Why don't the Donetsk and Lugansk people go to
Почему донецки и лугански не едут
defend ku here no one has them  I saw I don't
защищать ку у нас их никто не видел я не
know where they are there like where are they Kida you so I'll
знаю где их там типа куда их Кида те так
say what could be How exactly
скажу что может быть Как именно
there are no Luhansk Donetsk battalions but
батальонов луганских донецких нету а
namely Luhansk Donetsk boys m
именно луганских донецких пацанов м Ты
What are you talking about
что вот
these Akhmatovs were here before August 6
этих Ахматов тут было было до 6 августа
August 6 everything is with us in short they I don't know
6 августа все у нас короче они я не знаю
how are they with you? In Kursk, they
как они у вас У нас они в Курске
danced the lezginka on the Central
лезгинку танцевали на Центральной
Square, our girls, in short, Mali. In short,
площади девок наших короче Мали Короче
everything was like August 6th, they were stupidly
всё как только 6 августа они ту тупо все
recording videos, now we're pouring them out there,
записывали видосики сейчас там разливаем
and so on. It was, of course,
и так дальше Это был конечно
like Well, in fact, it's really harder than with
типа Ну на самом деле правда тяжелее чем
Yes in  I mean it makes you feel heavier
у Да в смысле вас тяжелеет так у нас
like we have a war here I mean
типа у нас тут блин война Я имею в виду
the truth that you say makes it heavier than
правда которую ты глаголишь тяжелеет чем
realizing that
её осознавать что
they are, well, everyone is afraid of them  no one
они ну ну их все боятся им никто вот так
will say it to your face, you know, I served, they
в лицо не скажет понимаешь я служил они
filmed TikToks. Listen, this is not a blogger,
тиктоки снимали Слушай это не не блогер
not a blog,
не блог
but it would be normal to put
а что нормально было бы выставить
someone there, I understand. Like from Ukraine.
кого-то там понял Типа с Украины Может
Maybe we can do it like this. Well, everyone, like a shop,
бы у нас получается как Ну все типа шопа
talks about them there, yeah. But  out loud like
там общаются про них да Но вслух типа ну
well, not even the deputies, no one local will
как бы не депутаты даже никто местные
say anything against the Chechens. So
против чеченов ничего не скажет Так
naturally, their position is What is it,
естественно у них позиция Какая сразу их
in short, and you know, in our Kursk
короче причём знаешь у нас вот в Курской
region, not a single dead or wounded
области ни одного погибшего и раненого
Chechen. No, where can I even say anything about all
чеченца Нет вообще где мне вообще за всё
my Show me at least one Chechen
сво Покажите хоть одного чечена не
Kadyrov is not the one saying he has an army of 80,000
Кадыров рассказывает у него 80.000 армии
Kai,
Кай
that's how they only give them money Listen,
она вот так только бабла им дают Слушай
what do you have going on
а что у вас получается
with Kiev, it was like that because for us, I was
типа с Киевом там было потому что нам я
like, up until the year I was like, what's
вот до дго года мне вообще было как что
going on there, and then this war started,
там происходит а потом началась война
Well, what year?  Maidan happened
вот эта Ну вчем году Майдан произошёл
in short the essence What kind of Yanukovych we had was the
короче суть Какая Янукович у нас был
president of
президент
Ukraine
Украины
when the sweat question
когда пот вопрос
Well yes that is the European Union or the
Ну да то есть Евросоюз либо же онат
Customs Union with Russia
Таможенный союз с Россией
accordingly Yanukovych is already going to
соответственно Янукович Уже собирается
accordingly Yanukovych is already going tosign an agreement with Well, that is, with the European Union, Putin is approaching the accession to it, they talked about something and, as a result, Yanukovych abruptly concludes an agreement on a customs union with Russia, accordingly, people in Kyiv gather and begin to protest because everyone wanted to go to Europe, Well, they are always for that euros they were there all these Europeans accordingly people rose up began to protest accordingly began to burn there like TV Hammer police officers there and so on and so forth Well in general one continuous rebellion and civil revolution of power I will interrupt you I was in the ninth grade when Ukraine was still there we went on excursions in short to Lviv Well, we came to Lviv to see there back and forth, the teachers told us you don't speak Russian to them Because if you say it in Russian, I'll show you something like go in the other direction or something else, we were standing at the station and they were talking there, although we on the one hand we have been in the ninth grade we are still schoolchildren they say something like that the position would be in the general distance Yanukovych accordingly leaves the post of president and leaves for Russia accordingly his temporary place
подписывать договор с Ну то есть с
occupy Turchinov This was one of the
занимают турчинов Это был один из
deputies of this
депутатов вот этой
Ukrainian Wait wait and he he did not
украинской Подожди подожди а он он не
go there to Lugansk Donetsk to his
поехал там в Луганск Донецк на свою
homeland and I can not
родину и не могу
understand the matter is not in the Homeland he was looking for
понять дело не в Родине он жеж искал
political asylum because there
политического убежища потому что там уже
was already a threat to life and health everything Well
шла угроза жизни и здоровья всё Ну
look if  I understood there you were for Yanukovych
смотри если я понял там вы за Януковича
like Donetsk Lugansk yes Ache he didn't
были типа Донецк Луганск же да Аче он не
come to Donetsk and Lugansk the matter there is not
приехал в Донецк и Луганск дело там не
Donetsk and Lugansk there is just you understand
донецко и луганс там просто ж понимаешь
What is the essence of the difference throughout Ukraine and
В чём суть разницы по всей Украине и
There were also in Donbass supporters of the fact that
Бывали и на Донбассе сторонники того что
they want to join the
они хотят в
European Union you understand  Well, why can't I just
Евросоюз понимаешь Ну почему я просто не
understand how it turns out
могу понять вот просто как бы получается
that in Syria Assad just took off and ran away
это как в Сирии Асад взял и убежал
to Russia, in short, and that he didn't stay with
короче в Россию да что он не остался со
his people, although Yanukovych
своим народом тического Хотя Янукович
could have gone to Lugansk to create
мог бы поехать в Луганск создать
some kind of opposition, recruit people for defense,
какую-то там оппозицию оборону людей
and a confrontation  it would have gone
набрать и противостояние бы пошло бы
further but you see he didn't want it he
дальше но видишь он этого не захотел он
got scared and left That is he
забоялся и уехал То есть он получается
abandoned his own people like Voters are coming out
кинул своих типа выходят Избирателей
roughly speaking, yes, he threw it
рубо говоря так да он кинул
accordingly I also didnt understand, yes,
соотвественно Я вот тоже не понимал да
they say that he was afraid there, but I didnt
говорят что типа там он боялся но я не
understand that he was afraid in Donetsk then,
понял че он типа в Донецке боялся тогда
accordingly, after this,
да соответственно после вот этого вот
like Yanukovych left, the people of Donbass, that is,
как Янукович уехал люди Донбасса то есть
then its not just Lugansk Donetsk then
тогда это не просто Луганск Донецк тогда
so that you understand there were Kharkov Odessa
чтобы ты понимал было Харьков Одесса
Zaporozhye Kherson Donetsk
Запорожье Херсон Донецк
Lugansk
Луганск
Crimea all these these regions they
Крым все вот эти вот эти областя они
started to
начали
submit documents for the separation of
э подавать документы на отсоединение
Ukraine from Ukraine in the sense of submitting This is
Украины от Украины в смысле подавать Это
where such documents are submitted to
куда такие документы подаются проводи
conduct a referendum rerepublican
проводить референдум рере народное
vote of Ukraine and accordingly and
голосование Украины и соответственно и
accession to the Russian Federation
присоединение к Российской Федерации
or  creation I just I don't quite
либо создание Я просто я не совсем там
remember there in these I have there in my opinion you had
помню в этих Я у там по-моему у вас было
like this one who is now sitting in prison in
как вот этот что сейчас в тюрьме у нас в
Moscow Girkin Strelkov Yes, he
Москве сидит гиркин стрелков Да он же
came like in April of what kind of to you in
пришёл типа в апреле чего вроде к вам на
Donbass And after that began  these
Донбасс И после этого начались эти
referendums Well, roughly speaking, so
референдумы Ну грубо говоря так вот
accordingly, when
соответственно когда начались
referendums began to be held, as if everything was
проводиться референдумы как бы было всё
official, that is, that is,
официально то есть то есть в
people began to come to the administrations, please, did
администрациях начали люди приходить пож
I understand correctly at first it turns out
п я правильно понял сначала получается
this is the gun and then they
этон прил ружи а потом уже референдум
did the referendum yes No At first we initially we
делали да Нет Сначала мы изначально мы
ourselves people went out We went out with
сами люди вышли Мы выходили с
bats well well
битами ну ну
in short against Well this government which is in
короче против Ну этой власти который на
Ukraine which seized power in
Украину которая захватила власть на
Ukraine we wanted to meet Right
Украине мы хотели встречать Правый
Sector there was just the opposition of the right
сектор там была просто опозиция правого
sector of the nat Where are you  in the ninth grade
сектора нацио Куда ты в девятом классе
you say you were Where did you
говоришь был Куда ты
go people just gathered from all over the
выходил люди просто собирались со всего
administration decided to wait when they
постановили администрации ждали когда
came to sex I explain what it is These are
прит к сек объясняю что это такое Это
Ukrainian Western nationalists
украинские западен националисты в
as students They were supposed to
качестве студентов Они что должны были
come I just didn't see it I'm
приехать Я просто не видел это мне
interested in what's there Yes he's in now
интересно что там Да он бе сейчас в
on the internet the right sector should have
интернете правый сек должны были
arrived they have they have a black and red
приехать у них у них у них чёрно-красный
flag which How did you know ho said
флаг который Откуда вы знали хо сказал
that this
что там приедет этот
sector would arrive They were going to go on buses you
сектор Они собирались на автобусах
explain further you don't interrupt
объясняешь дальше ты же не перебивай
listen further Here is this same right sector
слушай дальше Вот этот же правой сектор
They have already as they say turned off  power
Они же уже как говорится свернула власть
they are going to like like like
они собираются как типа типа типа как
Ultra to come and restore order yes that
Ультра приехать навести порядки да то
is to say to seize the administration to restore
есть захватить администрацию навести
order Yes accordingly in Odessa in
порядки Да соответственно в Одессе в
Odessa one begins with holding like
Одессе начинается одни с проведение типа
referendum that is people come to
референдума то есть люди приходят
vote gathered like this right
голосовать собрались вот такие вот право
sector When in Odessa there was no
сектора Когда в в Одессе не было
referendum at all not Listen it
референдума вообще не Послушай его не
was not why Because the administration of the
было почему Потому что администрация
building and the prosecutor's office
здания и прокуратуры
burned down then the UTS gathered and burned down
спалили то собрались утс и спалили
the building in Odessa the prosecutor's office in Odessa
здание в Одессе прокуратуру в Одессе
burned down Yes with people
сожгли Да с людьми
inside not  not that the Trade Union House is
внутри не не то там дом Профсоюзов это
not the prosecutor's office Well the Trade Union House That's
это не прокуратура Ну дом Профсоюзов Вот
accordingly they burned them down together with the people
соответственно вместе с людьми сожгли их
there in Kharkov they didn't let them seize Well ours
там в Харькове не дали захватить Ну наши
wanted to seize the Kharkov
хотели захватить харьковскую
regional administration and they weren't allowed There's
обладминистрацию и им не дали Там есть
a video of them arriving huts they put everyone down
видео их приехали избушки всех положили
And so there Oh I'm this video  I saw There it
А так там О я это видео видел Там же
turns out that this Motorola that
получается это вот этот моторол что на
you had a hero in Donbass, like yes He
Донбассе у вас был герой типа да Он же
was like in Kharkov at the capture of this
типа в Харькове был на захвате это
administration there is a video in short this well we
администрации есть видео короче это ну
can't tell Yes there is a video like they
не подскажем Да есть есть видео типа мне
showed me the same thing like because I
показывали тоже типа потому что я с
talked to Ukrainians they  like they tell me
украинцами общался они типа мне говорят
like there is I say tanu googled Yes
типа есть я говорю тану загуглил Да
indeed there is called in that Mola
действительно там называется в ту Мола
capture of the
захват
Kharkov administration  yes, it
Харьковской администрация да то он
turns out that he did not understand how he
получается я не понял как это он из
came from Russia already then in April, like
России приехал уже тогда в апреле типа
yes, to seize the Kharkov
да чтобы захватывать харьковскую
administration, it is generally unclear
администрацию что-то вообще непонятно
what he was doing there, the very essence of it is this listen
что он там делал сама суть Это слушай
further, accordingly, after these
дальше соответственно после вот этих
events, how they burned people in Odessa,
событий как они Сож людей в Одесской вот
this  here in the building of course naturally it
этом вот здании конечно естественно это
was all over the news and they started to
прошло по всем новостям и начали
take radical measures Well on our
радикально уже принимать меры Ну с нашей
part it's not like that look stop I
стороны соотве не так смотри стоп Я
just maybe I'm wrong it was in Odessa it
просто может я ошибаюсь это в Одессе это
was on May 2 you already had a war going on you on
было 2 мая у вас уже война шла уже у вас
April 12 the city of Slavyansk was captured 12  April
апреля город Славянск захвачен 12 апреля
was zakh Well, these are the ones who
был зах Ну стрелковым вот эти которые в
were put in prison by the shooter, they
тюрьму посадили сейчас
put him in prison now By the way, what he
посадили Кстати то что он
started to say for I also something I
начал говорить за Я что-то тоже я я
completely forgot he's like a hero of Donbass yes,
вообще забыл он типа герой Донбасса да
like it turns out and here he Put him in prison one of the
типа получается и тут его Посади один из
first start so to speak he just
первых начинай так сказать он просто
started in  recently I have already started to
начал в последнее время Начал уже
criticize the Russian command
критиковать российское командование
leadership Yes, similarly and accordingly
руководство Да подобно и соответственно
I know what I liked in short,
мне знаешь что нравился короче вот этот
you had this one, this brain, this is
у вас был этот мозговой вот это
real The car was driving, there was a machine gun
реально Ехала машина стоял пулемётный
crew, they initially already knew where it would
расчёт изначально уже знали где будет он
go and  his car
ехать и его машина
I doubt it anyway that they could
Это по-любому я сомневаюсь чтоб могли
build it in short Yes And it is not clear who
короче построить Да И вот непонятно кто
it is or is it Wagner or is it FSB officers who is
это или это Вагнера или это фсбшники кто
his plywood not even an FSB officer I
его фанера даже не фсбшник я тебе больше
will tell you more that in addition to normal
скажу что помимо нормальных типа
battalions like under the leadership of
батальонов типа как под руководством
Mozgovoy there were many battalions just like
Мозгового были много батальонов как раз
that  former bandits gang formations
таки бывших бандитов банда формирования
Yes militias they are like roughly speaking They
Да ополченцы они как грубо говоря Их
were called militias but nevertheless in the sense
назвали ополченцы но тем не мене смысле
wait then you just told me everything
подожди то у вас мне просто говорили всё
that these are miners like these are bandits it
что это шахтёры типа это бандиты
turns out Well militia militia but
получается Ну ополчение ополчение но
only we had the People's Militia
только есть у нас была Народная дружина
first went to
сначала ходили
patrol these brigades
патрулировать вот эти бригады
Yes, each city had
Да появлялись в каждом городе появлялся
its own commandant and they fought for the land,
свой комендант и дрались зак земли
accordingly, some of them are, that is,
соответственно некото есть то есть
the soldiers who fought, that is, the
Солдаты которые воевали то есть
militias fought with the Ukrainians, and at
ополченцы воевали с украинцами а они в
that moment they simply lived in the cities, power
этот момент просто города пожили власть
for themselves, cars, apartments,
под себя машины квартиры
everyone, their own gang, formations, and
вся кам го своя банда формирования и
everyone wanted
каждый хотел
their own Yes  and accordingly they immediately
своего Да и соответственно они сразу
caught from everyone these, that is,
выловили у всех Вот таких вот то есть
cool guys, that is,  with the money
крутых пацанчиков то есть при бабле
that was with the authority of some kind of
которые были при авторитете каком-то там
prosecutors former businessmen there
прокуроров бывших бизнесменов там
the owner of the store it
владельцем магази
turns out you were waiting were afraid of some of these
выходит Вы ждали боялись каких-то этих
right-wingers
правосеков
under the opposition that is in Mariupol
под оппозиции то есть в Мариуполе уже
people were already putting up barricades in front of the road
люди перед дорогой ставили Баррикады
so that ROSI that is Ukrainian troops would not
чтобы РОСИ то есть украинские войска не
pass
проходили
by the way not Well I saw  I saw There are also
кстати нево Ну я видел я видел Там же
the territories, in short, the Ukrainian territories were stormed,
теры короче украинские теры штурмовали
but the people were not armed, they
данно люди были не вооружённые они
simply did what the Ukrainian
просто как как сделало просто украинское
command, that is, the state, simply did. It
командование то есть государство просто
simply used the
Оно просто против мирных жителей
regular army against civilians. I see, this was on May 9, as it were.
регулярную армию я ви это на 9 мая
Yes, they simply sent the army to us,
походу было Да они армию просто нас
accordingly, as soon as
направили соответственно как только
poses there police building took weapons
позах там здание полиции взяли оружие
there Volunteers arrived from Russia
Там приехали Добровольцы с России по
arrived that is well Russian army
приезжали то есть ну российской армии
as in fact would not have arrived
как по факту не было бы приезжали
Volunteers
Добровольцы
accordingly began to take weapons old
соответственно начали заво оружие старое
of course to horror there probably from old
конечно до ужаса там наверно со старых
times from codes old somewhere in Lugansk
врем с кодов старых где-то в Луганска
Donetsk there that  -they got them from
Донецка там что-то по доставали со
the war, I don't know, there are probably Chechen ones
времён войны там не знаю ещё чеченских
there, well, there are rusty ones  Kalashnikovs and
там наверное вот ну там ржавые калаши
all that They took Kalashnikovs, set up the front
всё такое Всё взяли калаши ставили фронт
and that's it, a shootout
и всё началась перестрелка
began Did I understand correctly that it turns out
началась Я правильно понял что выходит
that these gangs,
что вот эти все бандформирования они
in short, they were robbing you Lugansk residents there Yes, there
короче блин там грабили вас же луганских
were some, there were some who
Да были были такие были такие которые
robbed But that's a small number of them, they
грабили Но это малость их было они
just got power, force  understood and Well I'm
просто получили власть силу понял и Ну я
saying as once again in each city there
же говорю как ещё раз в каждом городе
was its own commandant about us, let's say, we were
был свой комендант о нам допустим с
unlucky with the commandant we had him, he stupidly
комендантом не повезло у нас был он тупо
really robbed, he beat Luga And who would
реально грабил он избивал Луга А кто там
be there if not in Lugansk Well, in another city
был бы не в Луганске Ну другого города
we are from Anthracite, generally ourselves
мы с антрацита вообще сами
Anthracite Anthracite  - it's coal
антрацита Антрацит - это уголь такой
like that no no no that Well, this is a city a city
вроде не не не то Ну ан это город город
is called here so NCI coal such
называется у нас так нци уголь такой
honor coal then the division of power began the
честь угля потом началась делёжка власти
Cossacks came Yes the Cossacks began to make
пришли казаки Да казаки начали делать
their own rules to establish to make a village a village
свои порядки наводить делать станицу
this is some kind of d I also remember
станица это чекай какой-то д я помню ещё
that Dremov  dremov yes yes he was like that with
то дрёмов дрёмов да да он такой с
a mustache it was him yes
усиками был это он да
like
типа
hanging out O developed yes developed dremov is a
зависает О развила да развила дрёмов
good person in fact him too
хороший человек на самом деле его тоже
As they say some  from such bad
Как говорится одни из таких вот плохих
militiamen here I mean was he that died
ополченцев вот В смысле был он что погиб
yes yes he died on the second day of the wedding by
да да он на второй день свадьбы погиб
his own as his car was blown up also
своей же как в его машину подорвали тоже
blown up he got into the car
подорвали он сел в машину
like this listen and who of these
вот так слушай а кто вообще из этих
besides Strelkov who imprisoned him
кроме Стрелкова которые его посадили кто
survived  from these
вообще выжил из этих ополченцев
Donbass militias Well, exactly such famous ones,
Донбасса Ну Именно таких знаменитых
no one, no one, they all got rid of them,
никто никто всех убрали всех убрали
they all got rid of the ideological ones,
идейных всех убрали
what a joke, yeah, it's just strange,
да что за прикол да Просто странно
strange, the coincidence of all the ideos, first
странно совпадение всех иде сначала
Mozgovoy died, then Dryomov died, then
погиб мозговой потом погиб дрёмов потом
Motoro died, then Givi died,
погиб моторо потом потом погиб Гиви
then Zakharchenko died, Batman too, BT Yes,
потом погиб Захарченко Бэтмен тоже БТ Да
and that's it  there and that's all, I mean, and Zakharchenko
всё и там и всё в смысле а Захарченко
blew it up exactly the same way, they blew it up in a cafe, they
взорвал точно его же в кафе взорвали
blew it up in the city center, and I
его кафе взорвали в центре города и я
doubt that
сомневаюсь что это украинцы типа
it was the Ukrainians who were sneaking in there. Why not? It was the Ukrainians. In
там Почему нет это это были украинцы в
any case, I'll tell you this: This does
любом случае я тебе так скажу что это ж
n't mean that if you  you live in Donetsk
не значит что если ты живёшь в Донецке
you don't support the Ukrainian
ты типа не поддерживаешь украинскую
side there were such people radicals they
сторону были такие люди радикалы Они
could or couldn't and the special services and
могли не могли и спецслужбы та где
anywhere they could take a piece of plastic
угодно Они могли взять пласти кусок
plastic put it under the lamp and
пласти та положить под светильник и
blow it up it's just how did they know that
взорвать это просто откуда они знали что
it would be in this Well yes it's in any case
он будет в этом Ну да это это по-любому
their own you understand
свои понимаешь это
it's already actually a question of money that's
это уже на самом деле вопрос денег вот
how if you take that is someone
так вот если взять то есть кого-то
bought took did Everything well how  according to rumors,
купили взяли сделали Всё ну как по
they caught everyone, they just didn't give it, they didn't
слухам всех поймали не просто не дали не
give it publicity because you know, the World Cup is
давали это огласки потому что знаете в
the essence of the joke. Here the Ukrainians say that it was
ЧМ суть прикол Вот украинцы говорят Это
yours who removed it, the court itself, why the eyes, it
ваши убрали сама суд почему глазки это
wasn't given. Well, imagine how this will
не давалось Ну прикинь какого это
raise the fighting spirit of Ukraine when they
подымет боевой дух Украины когда они
find out that they removed all
узнают что они по убирали всех идейных
our ideological ones.  hero here and now
наших геро вот и ну
prist pony time gi Zakharchenko and other icons
приста пони врем ги Захарченко ины иконы
Yes these are icons icons because they
Да это иконы иконы потому что они
won every battle practically they
побеждали каждой битве практически они
Motorola defended this Donetsk airport
моторол отстоял этот Донецкий аэропорт
they sat there they defended it there they
они сидели там они там него отстояли они
recaptured it Givi tank
его отбили Гиви танковый
battalion smashed them just fluff and dust
батальон разбивал их просто Пух и прах
there was no  what kind of tank battalion does he have
там не было у него какой батальон
Samali where from where did
танковый самали откуда Откуда танки у
you get your tanks Oh, we had tanks, the tank
вас были О вот были у нас танки танковый
battalion is called Samali wait
батальон самали называется подожди
where did you get your
откуда у вас
battalion Yes, the tank battalion Samali
батальон Да танковый батальон самали
where from  the militias have a tank, it's Zhenya Kalash
откуда у ополченцев танке это Жени Калаш
Well, it's clear where they came from,
Ну понятно откуда ж появились откуда-то
tanks came from somewhere Well, where did the tanks come from Sorry,
танки Ну откуда появились танки Извини
friend, we won't tell you because we
друг мы тебе не скажем потому что мы
don't know ourselves, that's all,
сами не знаем вот и всё
accordingly, the battalion was called Sparta
соответственно батальон назывался Спарта
I just thought that they
Я просто думал что там типа стрелковым
fought with small arms there, everything  this time tanks nett
оружием воевали всё это время танки нетт
were tanks Potri video
были танки Потри видео
gods for example battles tank battles Well I
боги к примеру бои танковые бои Ну я
understand there for example they could get somewhere there
понимаю там например могли где-то там
secretly in short from the warehouse rusty
достать тайно короче со склада ржавые
machine guns but the tank is not in the store it is in
автоматы но танк это не в магазине он
any case
стоит это по-любому
g you know like surplus of war Echo of war  how
г знаешь как излишки войны Эхо войны как
was it officially tanks noma ponies
там официально танков было номы пони
remove Well, no matter how stupid it
убирать Да ну как бы глупо это не
sounds And when you Well imagine this you
звучало И когда ты Ну представь это
know there were icons on us and
знаешь были на нас иконы и дили то есть
they hung that is they were all loved and respected there
они висели все их любили и там уважали
As they say heroes and just Then you
Как говорится герои и просто Потом ты
just all over the whole  the internet and all the media
просто на всю весь интернет и весь СМИ
You're just saying that the Ukrainian
Ты просто говоришь о том что украинские
special services are killing the hope of Donbass,
спецслужбы убивают надежду Донбасса
so no one made this
соответственно никто не давал этому
public, everyone started talking Yes, yours,
огласки все начали говорить Да вот ваши
yours, yes, No  true I understood it all I'll give it to you in a
ваши да Не правда это всё понял Сейчас
minute Hello Yes
минуту суну Алло
Zelensky was vaccinated Senya 25th of January
Да привита Зеленского Сеня 25 сичня
today is his birthday I'm vaccinated
сегодня день народження У него привита я
now Lugansk
зараз Луганска
once everything is fine I'll call
раз всё я пизнише позвоню
Let's
Давай
continue Glory to
продолжим Слава
Ukraine okay okay thank you thank you for the
Украине ладно лад дякую дякую вам за
talk Let's talk Let's talk it
розмову Давай поговори Давай поговорим
was bomb That's the truth it
была бомбезна Вот такая правда да
turns out  no right sector not
оказывается никакие правосеки не
Ukrainian but their gangs Yes
украинские а ихний бандформирования Да
they robbed along the rivers here you have it all tank
грабили по речкам вот вам всё танковый
battalion And so on Here you have
батальон И так дальше Вот вам
evidence all like squeak ko This is
свидетельства все лайк писка ко Это
skill from
мастерство от
Aro subscribe to direct now axis VN
Аро подпишись на пря зараз ось ВН
apok this is very and very important YouTube zany
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through SRG ORV your ban  and I
нас через срг ОРВ твый бан и дуже багато
don't show people a lot of videos sometimes I don't show
вдео не показую людям вчасно не показуе
information about streams so that
информация про стримы тому для того щоб
we Mali can write operational links
мы Мали оперативный звязок пишиться
right now and while there are videos in Telegram OKM there are
прямо зараз а пок там в телегра окм
also videos  interesting and useful information
видео ще теж цикава и корисна информация
and we will oblige you with constant
и мы повинни з вами тримати постийний
operational links
оперативный звязок
independently in that che will show you about This
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про Цей
YouTube Glory to Ukraine
YouTube Слава Украине
signature L
пидпись L